mspidy.com 2018-12-26

# Privacy & Policy - Mspidy Share Your Stories gives Social Media News and Web Tips

Sign-In Information:

When you create an Account or login using your Twitter and/or Facebook credentials, you will provide information that could be Personal Information, such as your username, password and email address. You acknowledge that this information may be personal to you, and by creating an account with Mspidy and providing Personal Information to us, you allow others, including us, to identify you and therefore may not be anonymous. We may use your contact information to send you information about our Services, including without limitation, notifications regarding the Services and, upon your request, email digests of content shared by those that you follow on Mspidy, Twitter, and Facebook. You may unsubscribe from these messages through your Account settings, although we regardless reserve the right to contact you when we believe it is necessary, such as for account recovery purposes. 

User Content and URL Information:

Mspidy allows you to provide content to Mspidy, such as the ability to Mspidy and Submit collections of content and uniform resource locators ("URLs"), written descriptions of content or URLs, comments, text, images and video. We also collect and store information regarding the content in your Mspidy, Twitter, and Facebook feeds and the original URL, and associate that information with your Account. We also collect and store (i) the time and date on which the content was first place or liked, submitted, or shared and (ii) information on the channels through which the content was shared, e.g., to other Mspidy users, Twitter followers, and/or Facebook friends. 

We share certain information about you, such as your username, any avatar or image you elect to post, your Twitter and/or Facebook username, your reading feeds through Mspidy, Twitter, Facebook and other Third Party Services, and other information you elect to make public to your followers in Mspidy, your followers on Twitter, and your friends on Facebook,. This may include Personal Information, but only to the extent that you decide to share such information with others. 

We may retain content submitted by you to Mspidy indefinitely, even after you terminate your Account. 

Metrics and Analytics:

We collect information about accesses of content curated through Mspidy. This information includes, but is not limited to: (i) the IP address and physical location of the devices accessing the curated content; (ii) the time and date of each access; and (iii) information about sharing of curated content. 

Information Collected From Third Party Services:

Some features of Mspidy allow you to share your Mspidy curated content through Third Party Services and your content from Third Party Services through Mspidy. If you choose to connect Mspidy to such Third Party Services, we may collect information related to your use of those Third Party Services, such as authentication tokens that allow us to connect to your Third Party Service accounts. We may otherwise collect information about how you are using Mspidy to interact with those connected Third Party Services. Note that Third Party Services may have the ability to restrict the information that is provided to us. 

IP Address Information and Other Information Collected Automatically:

We automatically receive and record information from the Mspidy application or your web browser when you interact with Mspidy, Including your IP address and cookie information. This information is used to facilitate collection of data concerning your interaction with Mspidy (e.g., what content you have clicked on). 

Generally, Mspidy automatically collects usage information, such as the number and frequency of users accessing Mspidy and various curated streams of content. We may use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, but not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us and third parties authorized by us to figure out how often individuals use parts of Mspidy so that we can analyze and improve them. 

Information Collected Using Cookies:

Cookies are pieces of text that may be provided to your computer through your web browser or application when you access a website or service. Your browser stores cookies in a manner associated with each website or service you visit. We use cookies to enable our servers to recognize your web browser or Mspidy application and tell us how and when you visit and use Mspidy through the web or through an application. 

Mspidy cookies also allow us to track when you have accessed content through Mspidy. Each access is tracked using a unique identifier assigned to you in one or more cookies stored by your web browser or application and associated with Mspidy.   
Mspidy cookies do not, by themselves, contain Personal Information, and we do not combine the general information collected through cookies with other Personal Information to tell us who you are. As noted, however, we do use cookies to identify that your web browser or application has accessed content through Mspidy and may associate that information with your Account if you have one. 

This Privacy Policy covers our use of cookies only and does not cover the use of cookies by third parties. We do not control when or how third parties place cookies on your computer or device. For example, third party websites may set their own cookies. 

Aggregate Information:

We collect statistical information about how people use Mspidy ("Aggregate Information"). Some of this information is derived from Personal Information, such as your location (which, in turn, can be derived from your IP address or through location based services used by your device). This statistical information is not Personal Information and cannot be tied back to you, your Account, your web browser or your Mspidy application. 

How and To Whom Is My Information Shared?

Mspidy is designed to help you share information that you or people you choose to follow locate on the web with others. As a result, much of the information generated through Mspidy is shared publicly or with third parties. All Mspidy content is public. Your activity on the Mspidy network is public and can be distributed to anyone that follows you. We may also distribute content and feeds through an email digest to users who have elected to receive such email digests. 

Public Mspidy Activity Information:

Much of your activity on and through Mspidy is public by default. This includes, but is not limited to: 

URLs that you have "Share" or URLs submitted to Mspidy. 

URLs within your feeds from Third Party Services that you access through Mspidy and feeds from third parties that you elect to follow. 

Content that you have selected to curate on your Account, the corresponding URL(s), the time and date that content was curated, and metrics and analytics information for your curated content, as described above; and 

Aggregate non-personal information about what content you have accessed through Mspidy and associated metrics and analytics information, as described above. 

Some of this information may be associated with your Account and some of this information is publicly accessible to other Mspidy users who choose to follow your curated content. This information may still be accessible through other means, such as our API services. 

Please also remember that if you choose to provide Personal Information using certain features of Mspidy, then that information is governed by the privacy settings of those particular features and may be publicly available. Individuals reading this information may use or disclose it to other individuals or entities without our control and without your knowledge. Therefore, we urge you to think carefully about including any specific information you may deem private in content that you create or submit through Mspidy. 

Information You Elect to Share:

In addition to reviewing this Privacy Policy, you should also review the terms of services and privacy policies of any Third Party Services that you access through Mspidy. Mspidy respects the privacy settings/ policies that you have selected with Third Party Services, and only shares information consistent with those privacy settings and policies.   
You may otherwise access Third Party Services through Mspidy, for example by accessing curated content. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices of these Third Party Services, and you are responsible for reading and understanding those privacy policies. This Privacy Policy only governs information collected on or through Mspidy. 

User Profile Information:

User profile information including your username, avatars or images you elect to upload and other information you enter may be displayed to other users to facilitate user interaction within Mspidy. We will not directly reveal users' email addresses to other users. 

Aggregate Information:

We share Aggregate Information with our partners, service providers and other persons with whom we conduct business. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners can understand how and how often people use Mspidy and their services or websites, which facilitates improving both their services and how we interface with them. In addition, these third parties may share with us non-private, aggregated or otherwise non Personal Information about you that they have independently developed or acquired. 

Information Shared with Our Agents:

We employ and contract with people and other entities that perform certain tasks on our behalf and who are under our control (our "Agents"). We may need to share Personal Information with our Agents in order to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, our Agents do not have any right to use Personal Information or other information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information with our Agents. 

Information Disclosed Pursuant to Business Transfers:

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the transferred business assets. Moreover, if we, or substantially all of our assets associated with Mspidy, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of us may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy. 

Information Disclosed for the Protection of Us and Others:

We also reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information as it reasonably believes is necessary to (i) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, (ii) enforce these Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations hereof, (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, (iv) respond to user support requests, or (v) protect our rights, property or safety, our users and the public. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and spam prevention. 

Information We Share With Your Consent:

Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information. 

Email Communications:

If you sign up for The Daily Mspidy email via the Mspidy website or in any other Mspidy application, you will receive an email once daily summarizing popular content on Mspidy. Mspidy users that follow you will occasionally receive email digests that include information about what you have shared through Mspidy. 

Regardless of whether you decide to receive The Daily Mspidy, as part of Mspidy, you may occasionally receive from us email and other communication relating to your Account. These emails will only be sent for purposes important to Mspidy, such as password recovery. 

We may receive a confirmation when you open an email from us. We use this confirmation to improve our customer service. 

Is Information About Me Secure?

Your Account information (including your Twitter and Facebook logins) is protected for your privacy and security. You need to prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account. 

We endeavor to protect Account information to ensure that it is kept private; however, we cannot guarantee the security of any Account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time. 

We otherwise store all of our information, including your IP address information, using industry-standard security techniques. We do not guarantee or warrant that such techniques will prevent unauthorized access to information about you we store, Personal Information or otherwise. 

What Information of Mine Can I Access?

You can access information associated with your Account by logging into the web version of Mspidy, or through the Mspidy application. You can adjust settings and privacy preferences through your Account settings. 

Registered and unregistered users can access all of the above information. 

How Can I Delete My Account?

Should you ever decide to delete your Account, you may do so by sending an email to [support@mspidy.com](mailto:support@mspidy.com) If you would like us to remove such stored information, please send us an email at [support@mspidy.com](mailto:support@Mspidy.com)

What Choices Do I Have Regarding My Information?

As stated previously, you can opt not to disclose certain information to us, even though it may be needed to take advantage of some Mspidy features. 

You can delete your Account or adjust your Account's privacy settings. Please note that we will need to verify that you have the authority to delete the Account, and activity generated prior to deletion will remain stored by us and may be publicly accessible. 

What Happens When There Are Changes to this Privacy Policy?

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we collect or use information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on or within Mspidy or sending you an email. A user is bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses Mspidy after such changes have been first posted. 

What If I Have Questions or Concerns?

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy using Mspidy, please send us a detailed message to [support@mspidy.com](mailto:support@mspidy.com)  We will make every effort to resolve your concerns. 

Last Updated Date Privacy and Policy: July 02, 2012
